Hey David, Dad bought strawberries.
Don't eat it now.
Wait a moment, I'll give it to you in a moment.  Eitor,
give me that strawberry.  You have to wash it,
man.
Look at this, Dad.  Let me eat
after I wash.  He can.
There's a grape missing.  No, it's not.
Look at things more closely.  No, Dad.  I think
this is the most fragrant strawberry I've ever
seen in my life.
Calm down, Eitor.  You have to wash it, son.
It's because I really like strawberries.
Which do you prefer?  Strawberries or
barbecue?  Ah, barbecue.  Is strawberries with
barbecue a good combination?   It
's delicious.
I'll get another one.  There won't be any strawberries left
for us to eat.
Wait a moment.
[music]
I really enjoy it when David plays the
guitar.  Father, wait for the prayer.
I'm not even eating yet,
but you have to wait, okay?  Heavenly Father,
thank you for the strawberries, the grapes, the
granola, the meat, the guitar, and the
cat.